(Raj:)I don't freaking
believe this!
(Howard:)Relax, it'll be fine.
(Raj:)No, you have to put
this back together
(Raj:)right now,
so I can return it!
(Sheldon:)You can't return it.
(Sheldon:)Howard wiped his bottom
with the warranty.
What?!
(Sheldon:)I think metaphorically.
(Sheldon:)But he was in the bathroom
for a while.
(Raj:)Howard, my father cut me off.
(Raj:)I have to get my money back
for this!
(Howard:)Calm down.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Raj:)Okay, you're right.
(Raj:)It's time for me to step up
(Raj:)and take responsibility
for my life.
(Raj:)Be a man.
(Raj:)Hello, Mummy.
(Mrs Koothrapalli:)Hello, Rajesh.
(Mrs Koothrapalli:)What a nice surprise.
(Raj:)Well, I've been
thinking about you.
(Raj:)How are you doing?
(Raj:)Are you happy, Mummy?
(Mrs Koothrapalli:)Such a sweet boy for asking.
(Mrs Koothrapalli:)Can't believe you come from
the poison seed of your father.
(Raj:)Well, I like to think
I take mostly after you.
(Raj:)Anyway,
speaking of Daddy,
(Raj:)I had a very strange
conversation with him.